let's see the solution for the
performance comparison quiz we had a
laptop that takes four hours to compress
this video this is a latency so the
speed-up of new versus old will be the
old latency divided by the new latency
four hours is 240 minutes the new
latency is 10 minutes so the speed-up is
24 so the correct answer here is 24
intuitively a speed-up larger than 1
means that the new thing is actually
faster than the old thing speed ups less
than 1 mean that the new thing is
actually slower so if you divide the
wrong things here if you took for
example 10 over 240 you would have
gotten something like 0.04 and at that
point you can check the new thing is
actually significantly faster so if
you're getting a number that is much
lower than 1 that probably means you're
dividing the numbers wrongly